(Howard:)No idea.
Ask him.
(Raj:)12 minutes.
(Midwife:)12 minutes?
Why are you here?
(Stuart:)Aren't we supposed to get here
an hour and a half early?
(Midwife:)This is a hospital,
not the airport.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
It's our first time.
(Midwife:)It's okay.
(Midwife:)This little one will be
here before you know it.
(Midwife:)Do we know what
we're having?
(Howard:)No, we're keeping it
a surprise.
(Midwife:)Old school. Nice.
Not that old school.
He knows.
(Raj:)You see, I was
at the doctor's office,
(Raj:)the folder was right there,
so I took a peek.
(Howard:)And talking like this
(Howard:)doesn't make it less creepy.
(Midwife:)Sweetheart, go home.
(Midwife:)Come back when
the contractions
(Midwife:)are five minutes
apart for an hour.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry.
(Raj:)That's ambiguous.
(Raj:)Is it five minutes apart
starting at the top of the hour,
(Raj:)or five minutes apart starting
(Raj:)with the first contraction, so
essentially, like, 65 minutes?
(Midwife:)I'm just throwing
this out there,
(Midwife:)but home births are
very popular these days.